>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们潜水吧
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's dive in.
我们要谈这个关键词这个关键词可能是
We're gonna talk about the this keyword,
and the this keyword is maybe
所有 JavaScript 特征的最严重的困惑
the most perpetually confused
of all the JavaScript features.
如果我们在这里对所有人进行调查
I would imagine if we
polled everyone here, or
在网上看，或者以后看这个，你几乎肯定是
watching online, or watching this at
a later time, you've almost certainly been
在您的 JavaScript 职业生涯中某个时间点对此关键字感到沮丧。
frustrated by this keyword at some
point in your JavaScript career.
这很可悲因为它是一个非常强大的机制
Which is sad because it's
a very powerful mechanism, and
也很难过，因为它不需要这样。
it's also sad because it
didn't have to be that way.
不必说这会让我们困惑但
It didn't have to be that this
would be confusing to us, but
我想很多人被这个关键词搞糊涂了。
I think a lot of people got
confused by the this keyword.
仅仅是因为没有人告诉他们停止尝试使其成为此关键字的关键字
Simply because no one ever told them stop
trying to make it like this keyword in
其他语言。
other languages.
所以我觉得
So I think it's important for
我们要把这些东西放在其他语言上
us to set aside how these
things work in other languages.
并不是这些是不重要的背景，而是在它帮助你伟大的程度上。
Not that those are unimportant context,
but to the extent that it helps you great.
但在某种程度上其他语言行为会让你恢复
But to the extent that some other
languages behavior holds you back, and
使您更难理解或利用 JavaScript。
makes it so it's harder for
you to understand or leverage JavaScript.
那是你应该在门口留下的行李
That is baggage that you
should leave at the door, and
更具体地关注什么是 JavaScript ?
focus more specifically
on what is JavaScript do?
原来这个关键字是
Well it turns out that this key word is
比你想象的要简单得多
actually a bit more straightforward
than you would imagine.
它的威力比你想象的更强大
It's more powerful than you would imagine,
and it's just been explained and
教得不正确
taught incorrectly.
所以我们要给这个话题带来一些澄清。
So we're gonna bring some
clarity to this topic.
此函数表示或引用该调用的执行上下文。
A function's this represents or references
an execution context for that call.
正在进行调用的上下文。
A context in which that
call was being made.
这完全取决于调用该函数的方式。
And that is determined entirely
by how the function is called.
换句话说，这个关键字赋值，如果你看一个函数，
In other words, that this key word
assignment, if you look at a function that
在它中有此关键字，它是根据调用函数的方式分配的。
has this keyword in it, it is assigned
based upon how the function is called.
这就是反直觉的部分因为大多数人认为你可以看到
Which is the counterintuitive part because
most people think that you could look at
一个函数，并确定该关键字要指出的内容。
a function, and figure out what
this keyword is gonna point out.
但功能的定义根本不重要
But the definition of the function
doesn't matter at all,
以确定此关键字。
to determining the this keyword.
唯一重要的是如何调用该函数 ?
The only thing that matters is how
does that function get invoked?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 如果听起来很熟悉
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If that
sounds familiar to you,
因为我们已经谈论过一个灵活的可重复使用的情境。
it's because we've sort of already talked
about a flexible reusable context.
当我们谈论动态范围界定时我们谈论的是
It was what we talk about when
we talk about dynamic scoping,
以及你需要我们讨论的范围
and the scope you need of our discussion.
换句话说，这些关键字是 JavaScript的动态版本
So in other words, that these keyword
is JavaScript's version of dynamic
作用域是这样一种灵活的，可复用的行为。
scope if it's this way of having
as flexible, reusable behavior.
所以我有一个功能，就是这个意识，或者我很抱歉，
So here I have a function that
is this aware, or I'm sorry,
我没有这方面的功能
I don't have a function
that is this aware.
但你记得我有一个在动态范围内的功能
But you remember that I have
a function that in a dynamic scope
动态上下文感知。
dynamically context aware.
而不是要求老师在第 4 行引用老师的时候
So instead of asking teacher to get
the teacher, on line 4, when it references
老师，而不是用 1 个老师的方式，到第 8 行。
teacher, instead of trying to line 1
to get teacher, it goes to line 8.
因为请求是从第 10 行的另一个级别的范围调用的，
Because ask was called from line 10 it
was called from the other class scope,
这就是动态范围的作用
that's what dynamic scope does.
在 JavaScript 中我们有非常相似的东西
And in JavaScript we have
something very similar, but
它不是基于范围界限，也不是什么叫它的地方，
it's not based upon scope boundaries,
or where something's called from,
它是基于该函数是如何调用的。
it's based on how the function was called.
这就是我们要解决的问题
And that's how we're gonna
end up resolving it.
所以我在这里有一个版本的提问功能，
So here I have a version of the ask
function which is this aware,
它使用了这个关键词所以它就知道了
it uses a this keyword,
so it's this aware.
你会注意到我是从其他地方打来的
And you'll notice that I'm calling
it from some other location but
这不重要
that doesn't matter.
这不是我的电话我是怎么称呼它的
It's not where I call from,
it's how I call it.
如果我在这里用 ask.call ，我是说用这个
If I use ask.call here,
I am saying use this
作为此关键字的特定对象，并在该上下文中调用该函数。
particular object as your this keyword,
and invoke the function in that context.
因此，在此特定情况下，此关键字将指向我的上下文。
So this keyword in this particular case,
will end up pointing at my context.
你可以看到这种动态的灵活性在这里发生了。
So you see that sort of dynamic
flexibility happening here.
你看到我可以称之为同一个要求函数，很多不同的方法。
You see that I could call that same
ask function, lots of different ways.
并且为该关键字点提供大量不同的上下文对象，
And provide lots of different context
objects for the this keyword point on,
这是此关键字的动态灵活重用性。
that's the dynamic flexible
reusability of the this keyword.
这就是为什么它存在的原因
That's why it exists by the way,
it exists so
我们可以在不同的环境中调用函数。
that we can invoke functions
in these different contexts.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 原来有四种不同的方法
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So it turns out that
there are four different ways to
调用函数。
invoke a function.
这也许是对你的消息，因为你可能是
That might come as news to you,
because you might be
用于思考仅以一种方式调用的函数。
used to thinking about functions
as only being invoked in one way.
在 JavaScript 中，有四种不同的方法来执行此操作，并且每个方法都是
In JavaScript there are four different
ways to do so, and each one of them is
要回答这个问题，这个关键词是什么不同?
gonna answer the question,
what is the this keyword differently?
所以我们只需要学习这四种方法。
So we just need to learn those four ways.
在概念上，如果您可以回顾我们的讨论，
This keyword conceptually if you
can recall from our discussion,
这栋楼的隐喻
the metaphor of the building.
在词法范围的土地上，我们从现在的范围开始，
In lexical scope land,
we start at the current scope,
并在全球范围内工作
and work our way up to the global scope.
在这里我们要有一个不同的建筑
Well here we are gonna have
a different building involved.
我们要开始工作了我们要从大楼的底部开始
We're gonna start our way, we're gonna
to start at the bottom of a building.
但真正的问题是，哪一栋楼 ?
But the real question is, which building?
如果有人让你明天中午和他们见面他们说
If somebody asked you to meet them for
lunch tomorrow, and they said come
317号办公室见我你的第一个问题是什么楼
meet me in office 317, your natural first
question is gonna be, but what building?
因为有很多办公室 317在我的城市里
Cause there's lots of
office 317's in my city.
所以我们需要了解我们在讨论的具体背景
So we need to understand which
particular context we're talking about
在我们了解这方面的情况之前
before we understand how we look for
things in that context.
而最关键的问题是我们的关键词规则会告诉我们什么。
And the which building question is what
our this keyword rules are gonna tell us.